<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CodingKoala&#39;s Space</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CodingKoala&#39;s Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ZKTeco BioTime Missing Authentication</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve202230515/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve202230515/</guid>
      <description>During a recent penetration test, I stumbled upon an instance of the ZKTeco BioTime web application. This application was linked to a time punch clock taking pictures of employees. The management can then analyse these pictures through the web application or an app.&#xA;Through some directory fuzzing, I discovered the world-readable directories /files/photo and /files/biophoto. These directories contained the aforementioned pictures, which were viewable without authenticating to the web app. Since the filename structure used in the web application was incremental, brute-forcing all images present was trivial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tangro BWF Multiple Vulnerabilties</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tangro-bwf-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tangro-bwf-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <description>Together with Tobias Györfi, I tested the software Tangro BWF for a client in 2020. This is a repost of the security advisories that were originally posted on the blog of my former employer Thinking Objects GmbH.&#xA;Key Value Product Tangro BWF Vendor tangro software components GmbH (Heidelberg, Germany) Tested Version 1.17.5 Fixed Version 1.18.1 Mitigation Update to version &amp;gt;= 1.18.1 Adding Attachments to Arbitrary Workitem Key Value Vulnerability Type Insecure Direct Object Reference CVSSv3 Severity AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N (Score 4.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
